123movies.online 2018-10-03

# Privacy Policy - 123movies

### Privacy Policy

### **Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18. Under our Terms of Service, children under 18 are no allowed to access our service. 

**Collection of Personal Information**

On visiting this site, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Importantly, IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Links to third party websites**

We have included links on this site for your reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. 

**Policy Changes**

Megabox.li reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy, and will post any revisions on the Site. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy. 

**How to contact us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us [here](http://www0.123movies.online/page-contact-us).
